Downloaded from
Kisskh.love
There was
an announcement today
of a breakthrough
at the Institute
for Extraspatial Studies.
Researchers there have learned
Official Kisskh movies site:
Kisskh.love
of new energy sources
found in previously
unknown dimensions.
Tonight,
on the Benny Anger Show.
Citing rising tensions
with the Soviet Union,
scientists have moved
the Doomsday Clock
to 60 seconds to midnight.
Are we truly so close
to nuclear annihilation?
But first, we ask
the average citizen,
"Is America ready for war?"
So The Gazette
has this nuclear-attack
procedure article.
It says dead family members
should be wrapped
in garbage bags
and placed outside
for collection.
It sounds like
America getting ready for war
means Americans
getting ready to die.
Getting ready to die.
It's beautiful work.
I hope that ship
keeps it properly refrigerated
on its voyage.
If it decays--
It's plenty cold
where it's headed.
After two years
on this godforsaken island
creating the thing,
he'll make sure
it doesn't spoil
before the big reveal.
But, Ms. Manish,
I thought you'd be glad to see
the back of that damn thing,
not sketching the front.
Well, Mr. Shea,
I just wanted
some final sketches
of the facial assembly,
especially that amazing
beak structure.
"Amazing"?
You sound like
the scientists down there.
So caught up
in their own accomplishment,
blind to the horror
of this monstrosity
we dreamed up,
this nightmare they made real.
For one man's vision,
we've all gone through hell
and back.
But can we go back?
Think he'll let us off
this island?
We signed
the non-disclosure agreement,
we've been well compensated.
And our ship to the mainland
will be here in a few days.
Why such dark thoughts, Max?
Oh, well, yeah.
I'm sure you're right.
I guess in all this business,
there are more than a few
uncomfortable parallels
to an old comic book story
I wrote.
A vile little yarn from
Tales of The Black Freighter.
Adrift and starving,
my darkest imaginings
welled up unchecked,
spilling from brain to heart
like black ink.
Taxi!
I imagine Davidstown
overrun by The Freighter's
tattooed fiends.
My wife was almost
certainly dead.
I remembered her
and my beautiful daughters
waving goodbye
from the verandah.
Glad my Rosa
ain't alive to see this.
All now dead.
Everything's going to hell.
- Look at this. Look at this...
- Mm.
I imagined
my shipmates'
bloated corpses...
Doc Manhattan
leaves the planet...
...and the putrefying shark...
Russians
on the warpath.
...carrying
my raft to oblivion.
- Ozymandias attacked...
-  All dead.
I tell ya.
It all reads like headlines
from ten years ago,
before they banned
all the masked avengers in '77.
Hey, speaking of,
you see this Rorschach item?
They finally caught him
last week.
Turns out
he was a customer here, huh?
Ror-- I mean, Walter Kovacs?
Interesting.
Incredible, right?
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Makes you wonder
what makes a guy
like Rorschach tick?
Could probably go off
at any second.
Faced with
horrors both intolerable
and unavoidable,
I chose madness.
مهلا، تهدئة الأمر.
مرحبا، رورشاخ.
أنت مشهور جدًا هنا.
بالتأكيد سأحب الحصول على توقيعك.
لقد حصلت على قلم هنا.
إحصل على هذا الأحمق! اقتله!
تعال هنا يا ابن...
احصل عليه!
مزق هذا الرجل إربا!
لقد حان وقت الانتقام، رورشاخ.
اقتله!
كفى يا كوفاكس.
على الأرض!
لقد تم تثبيته! اتصل بالنسخ الاحتياطي.
هذا المكان على وشك الانفجار.
احصل على هذا الابن الزاني!
لقد مت يا رورشاخ، ميت!
لا أحد منكم يفهم.
أنا لست محبوسا هنا معك.
أنت محبوسة هنا معي.
و؟
اه دان؟
دان، هل أنت هنا؟
أوه، يا إلهي...
رائع.
واو!
يا إلهي!
- لوري؟ لوري؟ لوري! - و!
- لوري؟ - و!
- لوري! - و!
عيسى!
يتمسك.
لوري، هل أنت بخير؟
أنا آسف جدًا.
كنت أبحث عنك، و... و...
لا، لا. كنت... كنت فقط في...
هل أنت... هل أنت بخير؟
أعتقد أنني ضغطت عن طريق الخطأ على زر في...
كنت... كنت فقط أعبث مع آرتشي في وقت سابق،
- وتركته على... - أنا آسف. أرشي؟
نعم، سفينة البومة.
إنه لا... إنه لا-- هل أنت مصاب؟
حقًا...
- أوه. - أنا بخير.
آسف. واحد...
لقد-- حسنًا... لقد كنت قليلًا...
على الحافة في الآونة الأخيرة.
لم أكن سأقول ذلك.
أعني، منذ أن سمحت لي بالعيش هنا طوال الأسبوع.
ولكن نعم
لقد كنت تقفز على الظلال.
أعتقد أنني لم أرغب في التحدث عن ذلك.
إنه فقط...
بعد وفاة الكوميدي،
تعرض جون وأدريان وروشاك للهجوم خلال أيام.
لقد بدأت أشعر بالقلق--
أنت لا تأخذ هراء رورشاخ القاتل للقناع على محمل الجد،
- هل انت؟ - حسنًا، أم...
أوه لا.
أوه، دان، أنا آسف جدًا.
لا، لا، إنه... إنه جيد.
لقد قضيت أوقاتًا ممتعة في هذه البدلة، ولكن...
لقد ذهبت تلك الأوقات أدراج الرياح منذ زمن طويل.
هل تفتقد تلك الأوقات؟
الآن.
عند النظر إلى الوراء، كان الأمر كله محرجًا حقًا.
خيال طفل في المدرسة.
حسنًا، على الأقل كنت تعيش خيالاتك الخاصة.
لقد كنت أعيش وفقاً لرغبة والدتي.
حسنًا، بطريقة ما، أعني أن أحلامي كانت مزورة نوعًا ما
من مغامرات Minutemen.
لقد كنت أعشق هوليس،
الذي يتعارض مع خطط والدي بالنسبة لي.
أوه! أخبرني.
حسنًا... كان أبي يدفعني لاتباعه في العمل المصرفي،
لكنني فضلت الاحتفاظ ببطاقات النتائج
حول مكافحة الجريمة على العملة.
ومع ذلك، فقد ساعدني على التركيز، وتمكنت من الالتحاق بجامعة هارفارد.
كنت أدرس علم الطيران وعلم الحيوان عندما توفي.
وترك لي الكثير من المال.
مع عدم وجود أحد حولي ليقنعني بالتخلي عن هذا الأمر،
هذا ما حدث.
لقد جعلت أحلامك حقيقة.
حلم أصبح حقيقة
يصبح مجرد واقع فوضوي آخر، أليس كذلك؟
ولكن نعم
عندما كنت في تلك اللحظة، جعلتها ملكي.
أعتقد أننا جعلناها خاصة بنا.
هل ترى تلك الحقيبة التذكارية؟
كنت أحتفظ ببطاقة النتائج الخاصة بي
منفصلة عن مغامرات Hollis' Nite Owl.
كنت أكتب تاريخ مستقبلي بنفسي.
حسنًا، لم أستطع الانتظار للتخلص من كل تلك الأشياء
من أيام المغامرة الخاصة بي.
كما يمكنك أن تقول على الأرجح، صندوقي المحتويان على متعلقاتي
التي وصلت للتو من إخلاء روكفلر.
بصراحة، أنا مندهش من أنهم أزعجوا
أن ترسل لي أي شيء بعد... انفصالنا.
هل تفتقد جون؟
أنا أستمر في التفكير بأنني يجب أن أفعل ذلك.
حتى عندما كنت معه، لم يكن موجودًا حقًا أبدًا
على عكس جميع وكلاء الحكومة
يراقبنا.
عن كيفية إبقاء جون سعيدًا.
لكن، مهلا، لا أستطيع إلا أن أحلم بما لديك هنا.
أنت محظوظ لأنك تعيش بمفردك وتحافظ على خصوصيتك.
نعم...
محظوظ.
إنها مجرد حقيقة فوضوية أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
هل هناك نوع آخر؟
وهذه الأيام أشعر وكأن
الواقع ينهار من حولنا جميعا.
الآن تبدو مثل رورشاخ مرة أخرى.
دان، نظريته حول قاتل القناع لا تصمد.
غادر جون الأرض بمحض إرادته.
تم القبض على رورشاخ متلبسا بارتكاب جريمة قتل.
أين المؤامرة؟
ليس الأمر مثل رورشاخ أن تطلق النار على شخص ما.
سهل للغاية.
وتلك الأحداث كانت متزامنة بشكل وثيق
للهجوم على ادريان
ومقتل الكوميدي كان مصادفة أيضًا.
كان رورشاخ على دراية بهذا الأمر منذ اليوم الأول.
انظر، أنا أعلم أن هذا القناع قد أكل دماغه
على مر السنين،
لكننا عملنا معا.
كان رورشاخ دائمًا
محقق وتكتيكي لامع.
لذا، لا يسعني إلا أن أتساءل
إذا وجد أي دليل يربط كل هذه الأحداث.
أتمنى فقط أن أتمكن من معرفة ما يدور في رأسه.
حسنًا، والتر.
الآن، أعتقد أنك تعرف ما هذا؟
أريدك أن تنظر إليه وتخبرني بما تراه.
هل ستنظر إليه يا والتر؟
هل ستفعل ذلك من أجلي؟
ماذا يمكنك أن ترى؟
طائر جميل.
هذا رائع.
دعنا نحاول مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
ماذا ترى؟
- فراشة جميلة. - رائع، والتر.
يسير هذا الأمر بشكل جيد للغاية في جلستنا الأولى.
هذا يساعدني حقا على التحدث
للتأكد من لياقتك النفسية للاختبار.
دعونا نستمر.
ماذا ترى على هذه البطاقة؟
ولا تتردد في الوصف
كل الصور التي تخطر على بالي.
أوه نعم!
مهلا! اغرب عن وجهي أيها الوغد الصغير!
إنه لا يدفع مقابل رؤية وجهك القبيح.
إلى أين أنت ذاهب أيها الزاني؟
لا تلمسه!
من المحتمل أن يكون ابن العاهرة مصابًا بأمراض.
هذا صحيح أيها الزاني
ترجل!
حسنا ، والتر؟
ماذا تعتقد بشأن هذا؟
تستمر في مناداتي بـ والتر.
أنا لا أحبك.
اه... لا تحبني؟
سمين، ثري.
أعتقد أنك تفهم الألم.
سأخبرك عن الألم يا دكتور.
سأخبرك عن...
رورشاخ.
ولدت بسبب خطأ عاهرة،
تحت وصاية الدولة في سن العاشرة.
بعد مقتل والدتي، لم يتبق سوى ندم واحد في طفولتي.
عدم التواجد هناك للبصق على رفاتها.
أصبح عاملًا يدويًا في صناعة الملابس،
لقد تلقيت طلبًا خاصًا لفستان
في نسيج جديد من سلسلة دكتور مانهاتن.
السوائل اللزجة بين طبقات اللاتكس،
حساسة للحرارة والضغط.
العميل، كيتي جينوفيز، لم يستلم الطلب مطلقًا.
لم أعرف السبب.
الأسود والأبيض، يتغيران الشكل ولكن لا يختلطان.
لا يوجد لون رمادي.
جميلة جداً جداً.
في اليوم التالي، تم قتل كيتي جينوفيز.
اغتصبت وقتلت خارج شقتها.
سمع ما يقرب من 40 من الجيران صراخًا.
لم يفعل أحد أي شيء، ولم يتصل أحد بالشرطة.
حتى أن بعضهم شاهدوا.
لقد شاهدوا!
حينها عرفت ما كان عليه الناس
وراء كل خداع الذات.
خجلاً من الإنسانية، عدت إلى البيت.
أخذت فستان كيتي غير المرغوب فيه
وصنعت وجهًا أستطيع أن أتحمل النظر إليه
في المرآة.
1975، عملت في قضية اختطاف.
بلير روتش، عمرها ست سنوات.
مُخبِرين مُستجوبين.
واحد نزف الإجابات.
عنوان.
خياطة مهجورة في بروكلين.
لقد كنت حينها مجرد كوفاكس، أتظاهر بأنني رورشاخ.
ساذج، ضعيف، لم يفهم.
Until I found her.
Nothing left but pieces.
Ashes in stove.
Blood on chopping block.
Bones for dogs.
She was consumed by evil.
Never had a chance.
Neither did Kovacs.
Finally understanding
man's true capacity for horror,
Kovacs closed his eyes.
It was Rorschach
who opened them again.
Put dogs down easy.
They didn't know better.
Gerald Grice did.
What-- No. Hey!
Put him down hard.
I told you I didn't
do nothing to that girl.
You have nothing on me.
Come on, man.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Don't bother
sawing through handcuffs.
- Never make it in time.
- Oh, my God. You're crazy!
What... what,
you're gonna burn me?
You can't do this.
Stop! No! Oh, God! No!
No! No!
Once a man
has seen,
he can never
turn his back on it,
never pretend
it doesn't exist,
no matter who orders him
to look away.
I do not do this thing
because it is permitted.
I do it because I have to.
I do it because I am compelled.
I... I see.
No. You don't.
But have patience, Doctor.
You will.
How does Adrian do it?
He's barely older than I am,
but he's in better shape now
than I ever was
in my Nite Owl days.
Back when he retired
from being Ozymandias,
he had me and Jon up to visit
his Grand Antarctic retreat.
Such a show-off.
You visited Karnak?
Did... did you see Bubastis?
Yeah. He sent me off
to go play with his
overgrown house cat.
Genetically modified lynx, actually.
Fascinating.
The only fascination there
was between Jon and Adrian.
They talked endlessly.
He uses
his Veidt Enterprises fortune
to advance science.
- Nauseating.
- And fund charities.
He makes it seem so easy.
He retired from one fantasy
and just... built another.
He was... just born
with the answer
that no money or power
or a family can give you.
Answer to what?
After taking off the mask,
who are you?
Well, here's to Adrian,
the man with the answers.
Ugh.
Hey, what...
what's in your pocket?
Oh, I, uh...
rescued these from the fire.
My spare Owl Goggles.
Where were they?
In, uh... Archie.
- Archie?
- Well, nice that you two
are so familiar
after teaming up
to destroy my secret lair.
Here. Try them on.
Experience my Owl Vision.
No matter how black it gets,
when you look through these,
everything is clear as day.
Why, Mr. Dreiberg...
You're ravishing.
Oh, they must be broken.
Let me look...
I can't get the-- No,
got it. Sorry.
I'm... so sorry. It's not you.
- It's just...
- Hey, relax. It's okay.
- No, you deserve better.
- Dan...
- I mean, I really want this.
- It doesn't matter.
I know how it is
when something's not right.
We'll just sleep now. Okay?
Just sleep.
Coming up
on the eleven o'clock news.
Russian forces
push further into Afghanistan.
And Pakistan calls on the US
to intervene,
but Russia claims to be
merely securing her borders.
We also have a special report
on noted author Max Shea,
who mysteriously vanished
two years ago.
Hear why investigators'
search for clues
has ended in failure.
Well, well, well.
Hey there, Rorschach.
It's been a long time.
Big Figure. Small world.
"عالم صغير." يعجبني ذلك.
كما تعلمون، بعد 20 عامًا،
أعتقد أنك كنت تعتقد أنك تستطيع أن تنسى
ماذا فعلت بي.
أنت وذلك الرجل البومة اللعين.
من المضحك كيف أن هذه الأشياء
عد لتطاردنا رغم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
وبالمناسبة، الرجل الذي أحرقته يموت.
ربما غدا، أو ربما في اليوم التالي.
لكن انظر، كان لديه الكثير من الأصدقاء هنا.
وعندما يموت،
هذا المكان ينفجر ثم تموت...
بالبوصات.
طلب كبير.
الحمار الذكي!
سأمزق هذا الرجل حفرة جديدة الآن.
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا. لا داعي للاستعجال.
لقد انتظرت 20 عامًا.
سوف يحصل على مستحقاته قريبًا ولن يهتم أحد بذلك.
سمعت أن طبيبه النفسي استقال اليوم.
أنت وحدك في وادي الظل، رورشاخ،
حيث ماضيك له مدى طويل.
والشيء الوحيد بينك وبينه
هو واحد... قفل... سيء.
فكر في الأمر.
هل انت بخير؟
أحلام سيئة وواقع سيء.
أتمنى أن لا يكون هذا ما حدث في وقت سابق.
إنه الشيء القاتل للقناع.
تم إسقاط أربعة منا،
الحرب تلوح في الأفق
أنا... خائفة من أن يكون كل شيء متصلاً
والأسوأ لم يأت بعد.
ولا أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء لوقفه.
كل هذا يجعلني أشعر بـ...
لذا... عاجز.
لذلك، ركضت إلى هنا.
لكل الخير الذي فعلته.
إنه ليس مثل إخراج السفينة
يمكن أن يضع الأمور في نصابها الصحيح.
ولم لا؟
هل انت جاد؟
لقد كنت أيضًا منتقمًا مقنعًا، أتذكر؟
أنا معتاد على الخروج في الساعة 3:00 صباحًا
وفعل شيئا غبيا.
انتظر، أنا... لقد أحرقت بدلتك، هل تتذكر؟
نظارات احتياطية، بدلة احتياطية.
- و؟ - مم هم؟
انا مستعدة.
دعنا نذهب.
نأمل أن لا يتم القبض علينا.
واو!
هذا رائع، رائع حقًا.
دان، هناك مشكلة على يمينك.
يتمسك!
يبدو المبنى واضحا.
لا، انتظر.
- هناك! - شخص ما، من فضلك!
يبدو أنهم أربعة أشخاص بالغين. هل يمكننا أن نلتقطهم؟
بالفعل عليه!
من فضلك ابقى هادئا.
نحن هنا لإنقاذك.
ابتعد عن النافذة.
والدة الله!
والدة الله على حق.
أوه، أنا شبح مختلف تماما.
وبالتأكيد ليست أم أحد.
دعنا نذهب، من فضلك.
دعنا نذهب.
- شكرا. - شكرا.
- مرحباً بكم على متن الطائرة. - مرحباً!
أنت ذلك... الرجل البومة.
من؟
بومة مظلمة!
من يريد سماع بعض الموسيقى؟
أوه!
- السلام عليكم. - شكرا.
شكرًا لك.
ماذا حدث للتو؟
هل حدث هذا للتو؟
هل تعلم أنهم قد يسجنونا؟
مع رورشاخ لهذا.
نعم.
وربما تبدأ الحرب العالمية الثالثة غدا.
و!
- الليلة كانت جيدة. - كانت كذلك.
كنت أتمنى أن هذه الليلة قد توقظ شيئا بداخلك.
أوه، لقد فعل.
لا يشبع، أليس كذلك؟
إذن، ماذا ينبغي علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
ينبغي لنا أن نستعين باختبار رورشاخ.
ماذا؟
في هذياني،
يائس من الشركة،
تحدثت مع زملائي الذين لقوا حتفهم.
أصواتهم كانت تتكلم من تحت الطوافة.
محادثة الموتى، الكئيب...
يا رجل، عشرة أيام على الحرب النووية، ديرف.
- ...مريرة. - هذا ما قالوه على شاشة التلفزيون.
... حزين بلا نهاية.
يا يسوع، ديرف، فقط أحضر لي بعض كاتي،
حتى أتمكن من الحصول على ارتفاع، يا رجل.
أخبار سيئة لا تنتهي من الأفواه
حيث تنطلق الأسماك الصغيرة.
إنه ذلك الرجل من مانهاتن الذي جلب علينا هذا الأمر.
أوه! لقد وصلت للتو الأوراق الجديدة.
هناك أعمال شغب في السجن.
- أعطني هذا! - واو! هيا!
لقد حصلنا على أصدقاء هناك.
"حارس السجن يثير أعمال شغب ويقتل خمسة أشخاص"
رورشاخ مرة أخرى.
صنع العناوين الرئيسية
بعد أن ظهر بعض الأبطال الآخرين في الأخبار
لإنقاذ حريق المبنى.
لعنة الأقنعة!
هيا، دعونا نجمع الرجال.
سيكون هناك جحيم لدفع ثمن هذا.
إذا لم أكن أعرف أفضل، فسأقول أن الأمر كله مرتبط.
لقد تحدثنا معا،
أنا ورفاقي الفاسدون
من الحياة...
بائع الأخبار يشعر بهذه الأشياء.
...والنهايات...
كل هذا ينذر بالمتاعب.
...من الحكم الرهيب
علينا جميعا.
سوف نتعرض للقتل في الفوضى على يد رجال الشرطة أو المجرمين.
- على أية حال-- - لا، انتظر. انظر.
لقد خططنا بالفعل لتشتيت انتباه الحراس.
أعمال الشغب في السجن تؤدي المهمة بالنسبة لنا.
أستطيع الاستماع إلى مكالمات الشرطة عبر الراديو،
وسنحصل على معلومات استخباراتية دقيقة
حول المواقف والاستراتيجيات.
هذه تذكرتنا بالداخل.
إنه مجنون قاتل
آمل أن تثبت صحة هذه النظرية الطويلة الأمد الخاصة بك.
هل يستحق الأمر المخاطرة بحياتنا من أجل فهم اختبار رورشاخ؟
مم.
مؤخرتك في أيدٍ أمينة.
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك، فسوف أركلك.
في هوليس؟
أوه، فقط فكرت في التحقق بعد أن فاتتك
جلسة البيرة لدينا في الليلة الأخرى.
انا آسف، هوليس.
لقد انغمست للتو في قراءة كتاب.
قهوة؟
بالتأكيد.
إذن... هل شاهدت الأخبار مؤخرًا؟
لا يمكن تفويت العناوين الرئيسية
عن هذه الحرب يقولون أنها قادمة.
كانت هناك قصة أصغر بالأمس
حول حريق المبنى السكني،
وإنقاذ غير عادي للغاية.
لا لا.
- لا. - الآن انتظر.
- آه ها. - انتظر، انتظر، انتظر، انتظر، انتظر.
أنت تقول دكتور مانهاتن
هل كان مغادرة الكوكب مدبرة؟
توقيت بين الهجمات
عن بليك، وأدريان، وروشاخ، نعم.
إنه مجرد صدفة.
كان لا بد من تصنيع الهجوم الإعلامي على جون بشأن إصابته بالسرطان.
عاش لوري معه،
ولم تصاب بالسرطان أبدًا.
لكنني قمت ببعض الحفر.
ضحايا السرطان المذكورين في نوفا إكسبريس
لقد تم توظيفهم جميعًا في وقت ما من قبل نفس الشركة.
مرة أخرى، مصادفة للغاية.
أعتقد أن شخصًا ما استخدم هؤلاء الأشخاص المحددين
والصحافة تطالب بنفي جون،
وأعتقد أنها جزء من خطة
لبدء الحرب العالمية الثالثة.
واو! هذه نظرية بعيدة الاحتمال.
وقال لوري نفس الشيء أيضًا.
وهذه الشركة التي تربط بين ضحايا السرطان،
من هم؟
وكيف يتم ربطهم
إلى بليك وأدريان وروشاخ؟
اسم الشركة هو Dimensional Developments.
وراء الاسم، لقد ضربت جدارًا
التحقيق في هيكل شركتهم.
ماذا عن ادريان؟
إنه متصل بعالم الشركات
وسيكون بالتأكيد متحمسًا للمساعدة.
بدون أدلة أقوى،
مشاركة نظرية المؤامرة هذه مع رجل في منصبه
قد يضعه في موقف محرج.
أعني، هو... قد يضطر إلى الإبلاغ عنا، لكن...
لكنني أعمل على طريق آخر
هذا، آه، ينبغي أن ينفجر قريبا جدا.
أنا متأكد من أنك سوف تحل القضية، يا فتى.
إنني أ ثق بك.
وشكرًا لك على مشاركة التفاصيل.
مم.
أشعر وكأننا عدنا إلى الأيام القديمة مرة أخرى.
مهلا، علينا نحن البوم الليلي أن نبقى معًا.
حسنًا، هذا هو السبب الذي جعلني أقوم بزيارة، دان.
إذا تمكنت من معرفة من قام بعملية الإنقاذ
في حريق المبنى السكني،
ويمكن للشرطة أن تفعل ذلك أيضًا.
يا للأسف، لقد نفد وقتنا.
حسنًا، لا عودة الآن.
إذا لم نتمكن من حل هذه القضية،
ربما لا يكون هناك عودة لأي منا.
إذهب، إذهب، إذهب لقد تم إطلاق النار علينا.
الضابط سقط! الزاوية الجنوبية الغربية!
استسلم أو سيتم إطلاق النار عليك!
ألا تشعر بالسعادة لأنهم يبقونك في الحبس الانفرادي؟
الآن لن ينقطع اجتماعنا
من قبل الغوغاء هناك.
لورانس، اسرع مع اللحام القوسي.
ما الأمر يا رورشاخ؟ هل الجو دافئ للغاية هناك؟
حسنًا، سيصبح الطقس دافئًا جدًا.
نعم، لاحظت كيف فجأة،
إنه لا يعطيك أي شيء، "طلب كبير، عالم صغير"؟
ربما اكتشف ذلك بمجرد أن قطعنا هذه القضبان،
سنجعله أقصر قليلاً.
فرصة كبيرة.
سمين؟ أيها الوغد الحقير!
لدينا سجن مليء بالرجال هنا الذين يكرهونك بشدة.
ماذا لديك؟
ذراعيك.
مهلا! ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
لورانس، أنت ابن العاهرة الغبي!
الآن لا يمكننا الوصول إلى القفل.
عذرا، الشكل.
لا يزال مايكل قادرًا على قطع القضبان.
هذا سيستغرق وقتا طويلا.
لن يستمر هذا الشغب
ولا أريد أن أقاطع.
- آسف لورانس... - لا!
...ولكنك في طريق انتقامي.
- لا يا رئيس! - مايكل، اقطعه.
- لا، لا، انتظر! - ليس هناك شيء شخصي، لاري.
انتظر! مهلا!
واحد-لا شيء.
حركتك.
تعال وخذني.
هذا الشيء ليس ملكنا.
افتح النار!
قم بإسقاط طائرتك أو سنستخدم القوة المميتة.
وتقول إذاعة الشرطة أن هذه المنطقة تخضع لسيطرة السجناء.
سدادات الأذن في. ضرب الصراخ.
أوه!
أسقط هذا الشيء!
اسرع بهذا القفل.
أريد أن أشم رائحة هذا الابن العاهرة أثناء الطبخ.
ثم سأقوم بتقطيعه مثل ديك الرومي في عيد الشكر.
نحن في الداخل.
أنظر إليه
يتسلق على سريره مثل طفل خائف.
لقد حصلنا عليك الآن، أيها الوغد الصغير.
لم يتم التخلص من مياه الصرف الصحي مع المرحاض من قبل.
واضح، حقا.
اثنان لا شيء.
حركتك.
كيف سنجده في كل هذا؟
على افتراض أنه ليس ميتًا.
فهو يجتذب هذا الرعب والجنون.
هذا هو المكان الذي يعيش فيه.
ساعدوني! ساعدوا أحداً على القبض على هذا الرجل! ساعدوني!
مهلا، رورشاخ!
يا!
يساعد!
رورشاخ!
يا رجل، لقد جئنا لنخبرك.
عذرا، يجب أن أذهب إلى حمام الرجال.
أوه، من أجل المسيح!
حسنًا، عندما يتعين عليك الذهاب، يتعين عليك الذهاب.
انظر، لدينا أقنعة هنا!
هذه هي بومة الليل! احصل عليها!
مهلا! نحن نحاول ايقاف الحرب!
أعتقد أنني أشعر بالمرارة نوعًا ما بشأن...
خسارة المنزل.
من الأفضل أن أتصل بالسفينة عبر الراديو.
لقد فعلت ما كان يجب فعله.
أستطيع المغادرة الآن.
- هل أنت متأكد؟ - من هنا.
هل غسلت يديك؟
أرشي يغطي خروجنا.
هل استحممت؟
تم غسله مرتين.
مسدودة قليلا.
لا تدعهم يهربون!
تتبعهم بالأضواء!
هبط بطائرتك الآن!
أكرر! هبط بطائرتك!
الجميع سوف يبحثون عنا هنا.
أعرف مكانًا للاختباء والتخطيط لخطوتنا التالية.
يسعدني رؤيتك بالزي الرسمي، دانييل.
مثل الأوقات القديمة.
لم يعجبني زيّك أبدًا، يا آنسة جوسبيكزيك.
- لا شيء شخصي. - اه!
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أننا نتفق على شيء ما.
عيسى.
- مرحباً. - جون.
قالوا أنك كنت على المريخ.
أنا على المريخ.
لقد تم جدولة محادثة هناك.
سوف تحاول إقناعي
لإنقاذ هذا العالم.
هل يجب علي أن أقنعك؟
جون، نحن بحاجة ماسة لمساعدتك هنا على الأرض.
كل هذا هو deus ex machina.
الإله خارج الآلة. نعم، أعتقد أنه كذلك.
مع ذلك،
بعد ساعة من المستقبل، نحن نتحدث على المريخ.
- المريخ؟ ليس لدينا وقت-- - دان.
أعتقد أنه من الأفضل أن أذهب معه.
ربما نجد طريقة للخروج من هذه الفوضى.
سوف أكون بخير.
لوري، انتظري.
يعتني.
من المؤسف أنهم لن يعملوا معنا.
نعم، نعم، إنه كذلك.
نحن هنا.
ماذا تعتقد؟
أوه، بالطبع. سامحني.
في بعض الأحيان هذه الأشياء تفوت ذهني.
هل أنت بخير؟
يسوع! جون، أنت ابن غبي ل...
يا إلهي.
وهنا حيث نتناقش حول مصير الأرض.
والحقيقة أن الحياة جحيم...
ويد الموت الخشنة هي خلاصنا الوحيد.
لن أتحمل المزيد من الحوارات الصاخبة بين الأموات.
لا مزيد من هذيانات الإدانة.
لا مزيد من الأحكام على خطايانا.
...الحارس المعروف باسم Nite Owl،
دخل الشغب وأطلق سراح القاتل المشتبه به،
والتر كوفاكس،
ويعرف أيضًا باسم رورشاخ.
تمكن كلاهما من الفرار من قبضة الشرطة عبر طائرة.
آآآه!
المزيد من التفاصيل سوف تأتي لاحقا.
- يا إلهي! - ديرف! ماذا حدث؟
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا.
نحن لا نريد أي مشاكل هنا.
أسكت يا رجل عجوز.
هؤلاء الأوغاد الخارقون يفلتون من العقاب في كل شيء
في حين أن رجالنا يتعرضون للجحيم في تلك الشغب.
إنه ليس عادلا!
على الرغم من الخوف من مثل هذا اللون الأسود،
نهاية لاهثة، قفزت...
مرحبًا، ذكر رجل الأخبار Nite Owl.
...أقدامنا أولاً في البرد،
معدل الوفيات رطب.
ديرف، هو الرجل الذي كتب ذلك الكتاب عن الأقنعة.
والدي يأخذ سيارته إلى ورشة الإصلاح.
- هل تعرف أين هذا؟ - نعم.
إنه أسفل الشارع مباشرة...
لكن أعماق المحيط
رفض أن يبتلعني.
رفعت عيني غير المدركة إلى السماء
ورأيت بدلا من ذلك الأرض.
هذا الرجل يحب اللعب في أعمال الشغب...
لقد وصلت إلى وجهتي.
...لذا دعونا نعطيه شغبًا.
نعم، نعم، دعونا نعبث بهذا الرجل!
- الجحيم، نعم! - باه!
لقد تركوني للموت.
الشياطين الذين بلا شك ذبحوا أقاربي.
ولكن الآن عدت إلى قارب جثتي،
شبح الانتقام
ركوب المد والجزر إلى المنزل.
نعم نعم!
- هذا هو؟ - نعم، في الطابق العلوي.
حسنًا، حسنًا، أنا أسمعك.
يمكنك التوقف عن الضرب.
فقط أعطني ثانية واحدة.
-أمسكه! -نعم!
احصل على هذا الكلب!
اهتم بنفسك أيها الوغد.
لا.
- ديرف! - يا رجل.
ديرف! هذا يكفي!
لقد انتهى أمره، علينا أن نخرج من هنا!
هذا هو المكان الذي نجري فيه محادثتنا.
يبدأ الأمر عندما تفاجئني بالأخبار
أنك ودريبيرج تنامون معًا.
هل تعرف عني وعن دان؟
لا، ولكن بعد لحظات سوف تخبرني.
آه! جون، لا أستطيع أن أتحمل كلامك عن القدر
الآن.
لا معنى له
أنك يمكن أن تفاجأ بأي شيء
عندما يمكنك رؤية الوقت في جميع الاتجاهات.
كل شيء مقدر مسبقًا، حتى ردود أفعالي.
لذا فإن أقوى كائن في الكون
هي مجرد... دمية تتبع نصًا؟
نحن جميعا دمى، لوري.
أنا مجرد دمية يمكنها رؤية الخيوط.
لا يوجد مستقبل، ولا يوجد ماضي.
الوقت متزامن.
آه! جون، كيف يمكنني مناقشة مصير الأرض؟
متى تعرف النتيجة؟
ساعدني على الفهم هنا.
ما هي ذكرياتك الأولى؟
لا أعرف.
عندما انفصل والداي، على ما أعتقد.
لم يستطع أن يفهم
لماذا أحمل ضغينة...
أتذكر أنهم كانوا يتجادلون، ولكن...
إنه مختلف بالنسبة له.
ولم أعد أستطيع أن أتحمل الغضب بعد الآن.
يا إلهي، أنت بحاجة إلى علاج.
لا لقد ذهب.
لا، ليس كذلك.
إنه لا يزال هنا.
دع نفسك تراه.
انظروا، للمبتدئين،
he was there, okay?
And he was actually gentle.
I was five, I think.
Do you have any idea
what gentleness means
for a guy like that?
I snuck downstairs
to play with a snow globe.
It means
a broken marriage
and an uncertain future
for our child.
My child! That's what this
is all about, remember?
My dad was always
- yelling at me...
- Laurel Jane!
...because he knew
I wasn't his.
What are you doing down here?
Pretty sure my real dad
was Hooded Justice,
my mom's old boyfriend.
Anyway, I...
My dad
was a domineering bully
like most of the men
I've been...
But Dan's... not like that.
He's gentle.
Someone you can pour
your troubles out to.
A receptive lover.
You mean...
you're sleeping with Dreiberg?
But... you already know.
- You said--
- I said many times
that you were my only link,
my only concern
with the world.
What does it say
that when you left me,
I left Earth?
Now that you
have replaced me,
that link is shattered.
Don't you see the futility
of asking me to save a world
I no longer have
any stake in?
Jon, don't be ridiculous.
Earth's too important
to hinge on one relationship.
Not to me.
My red world here
means more to me
than your blue one.
I will show you.
Cowering down here
in sludge
doing nothing but conjuring
names on screens.
Computer unnecessary.
This face is all I need.
Give me smallest finger
on man's hand.
I'll produce information
about mask killer.
Hey, you needed
your spare costume,
I needed time for research.
And now we need to put
our heads together on this.
You said the Comedian
told Moloch about an island
and a plot against Jon,
and I think the plot
had to be the cancer-scare
media attack
that sent Jon off the planet.
Now, check this out.
I finally got a breakthrough
investigating
Dimensional Developments,
the company that employed
Jon's alleged cancer victims.
They also owned
the Institute
for Extraspatial Studies.
And look, Nova Express
is connected.
They published
the cancer list.
And all of these companies
appear to be funded
by Pyramid Deliveries.
Pyramid?
That means
something to you?
Moloch's illegal
cancer meds...
delivered by Pyramid.
God, Moloch was in deep.
And probably didn't know it.
If his place was bugged
by these companies...
They'd know about
Comedian's visit to Moloch.
And that Comedian discovered
the plot against Jon.
Know of my investigation,
know how to frame me.
- But what about Veidt?
- Hm.
The assassination attempt
on Adrian doesn't fit the--
Hold... hold on.
Location
is Mason's Auto repairs.
Hollis?
Additional units needed
to canvass the area
for Knot-Tops.
- Coroner en route.
- No.
Body ID-ed as...
- ...Hollis Mason.
Oh, God! Hollis?
Oh, Christ! No!
Sorry.
He was a good man.
I wasn't there.
I should have...
I should have been there.
It could be random killing.
Could be
another mask killer.
Squeeze underworld,
find answers. Take revenge.
No.
We don't have time.
We have to--
His own fault.
Was lazing too long.
Forgot how to do things.
Lazing? Lazing?
Who the hell
do you think you are?
أنت تعيش على الناس بينما تهينهم.
والسبب الوحيد لعدم شكوى أحد هو
لأنهم يعتقدون أنك مجنون تمامًا!
هل تعلم كم هو صعب أن تكون صديقًا لنفسك؟
دانييل، أنت صديق جيد.
وأنا أعلم ذلك.
أنا آسف لأن الأمر صعب في بعض الأحيان.
لا، أنا من يجب أن يشعر بالأسف.
لا ينبغي أن أقول كل ذلك.
دعونا ننسى ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
ليس لدينا وقت لهذا.
اتفقنا، النهاية قريبة.
وقاتل ادريان
هي القطعة التالية من اللغز.
دعونا نأمل أن يكون أذكى رجل في العالم
يمكن أن تساعدنا في جمع كل ذلك معًا
قبل فوات الأوان.
السيد الرئيس،
الدبابات الروسية تتجمع في ألمانيا الشرقية
ردًا على "التهويل الغربي" المزعوم.
تعتقد وكالة المخابرات المركزية أن هذا حقيقي.
لقد كان كلا بلدينا في حالة تأهب قصوى خلال الأسبوع الماضي.
شرارة واحدة ويمكن أن يشتعل كل شيء.
تحليلنا للضربة الأولى ضد صوامعهم النووية
يظهر فرصة جيدة للنجاح.
قد يصل عدد الضحايا من جانبنا إلى 10-20 مليونًا.
حسنًا، في الموجة الأولى، على أية حال.
قواتنا التكتيكية والإستراتيجية في جميع أنحاء العالم
هم واقفون على أهبة الاستعداد في حالة DEFCON 2.
ما هي تعليماتك يا سيادة الرئيس؟
هممم.
نحن نجلس وننتظر.
انظر، جون، ليس لدينا الوقت الكافي للذهاب في جولة سياحية على المريخ،
وهذا النقاش لا يتجه إلى أي مكان بسرعة.
هل يمكنك من فضلك أن تنقذني من هذا العذاب؟
وأخبرني كيف تنتهي هذه المحادثة؟
وينتهي بالدموع.
سأعود إلى الأرض في مرحلة ما في المستقبل،
وأجد الشوارع مليئة بالجثث.
ولكن التفاصيل غامضة.
ماذا؟
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "غامض"؟
هناك نوع من الثبات الذي يحجب المستقبل،
منع أي انطباع واضح.
النبضة الكهرومغناطيسية لتفجيرات الرؤوس الحربية الجماعية
من الممكن أن يسبب ذلك.
يا إلهي.
جون، لا يمكننا الطيران حول المريخ
إذا كانت الصواريخ على وشك أن تنطلق إلى الوطن.
ربما تكون البشرية على حافة الانقراض.
ألا يزعجك هذا؟
لا، لوري. هذا لا يزعجني.
الحياة ظاهرة مبالغ في تقديرها إلى حد كبير.
المريخ يتعايش بشكل مثالي بدون أي كائنات دقيقة واحدة.
سطحها عبارة عن خريطة طبوغرافية متغيرة باستمرار،
تتدفق وتتحول في تموجات يبلغ عرضها 10000 سنة.
يُطلق عليه اسم التضاريس الفوضوية.
نعم، حسنًا، حياتنا مليئة بالفوضى أيضًا.
أعني، فكر في المرة الأولى التي التقينا فيها
في ذلك الشيء Crimebusters في الستينيات.
...يتحدون معًا كـ Crimebusters.
هذا لا يعني القرفصاء!
هل تتذكر كيف انهار كل ذلك؟
لقد أصبح الأمر أكثر فوضوية بعد رحيلك.
لوريل جين، أليس كذلك؟ ابنة سالي؟
اه...نعم.
لقد لاحظت تصرفاتك هناك. لقد كنت رائعاً جداً.
هممم، أنت لم تكبر بشكل سيء للغاية.
شكرًا.
هل تتحدث والدتك عني كثيرًا؟
مم، ليس حقا.
أرقام.
لقد حصلت على عينيها،
حتى تلك الشامة الصغيرة.
ليس لديك شعرها، ولكن بخلاف ذلك فأنت مثلها.
أنت شخص جميل.
ارفع يديك عنها!
مرحبًا سال، لم نتقابل منذ فترة طويلة.
ليس طويلاً بما فيه الكفاية في كتابي.
هل هناك أعماق لا يمكنك الغرق فيها؟
كنا نتحدث للتو، ألا يستطيع الرجل أن يتحدث إلى...
ابنة صديقه القديم؟
ماذا تعتقد أنني؟
أنا أعرف ما أنت، إدوارد بليك!
لقد عرفت ذلك منذ 25 عامًا.
ولا تنسى ذلك أبدًا.
اعتقدت أننا قد حسمنا كل هذا منذ وقت طويل.
مثل هذه الأشياء لا يتم تسويتها،
وهذا لن يحدث لابنتي.
هيا، نحن سنغادر الآن.
بالطبع، في هذه اللحظة،
لم أعلم ماذا فعل هذا اللقيط.
لقد قادتنا أمي لثلاثة كتل...
...أوقف السيارة،
وبعد ذلك جاء كل شيء يتدفق.
ألمها ومخاوفها
وما فعله بليك لها.
لقد حملت ذلك معي لسنوات.
في مرحلة ما، عبرت مساراتي مع بليك
وبعض المشروبات كثيرة جدًا.
وكنت سكيرًا سيئًا.
جوسبيشيك، هاه؟
هل أخذت اسم جدتك بدلاً من كوكب المشتري؟
أرى أنك لم تأخذ اسم والدك أيضًا.
- ما هذا بالنسبة لك؟ - لا شيء.
لا أزال أرى والدتك فيك.
لقد كانت خوخة.
هل هذا ما قلته لها قبل أن تضربها؟
قبل أن تحاول اغتصابها؟
أي نوع من الرجال يجبر المرأة على ممارسة الجنس؟
ضد إرادتها؟
مرة واحدة فقط.
مع سبعة سكوتش في داخلي،
وواحدة في يدي،
لقد تركته يحصل عليه.
وبعد ذلك، غضبت،
وأخرجونا من هناك.
على الأقل حينها بدا أنك تفهم
التضاريس الفوضوية في حياتنا.
لماذا أصبح الأمر أقل أهمية الآن؟
لقد قرأت الذرات، لوري.
أرى المشهد القديم
التي أدت إلى ولادة العالم تحتنا.
علاوة على ذلك، فإن حياة الإنسان قصيرة وعادية.
أنا انتهيت.
أرض هذا الشيء.
خذنى إلى المنزل.
كما تريد.
قلت أن هذا سينتهي بالدموع.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
ربما كنت مخطئا بشأن الشوارع المليئة بالجثث أيضا.
لوري، لقد اشتكيت من أنني رفضت
رؤية الوجود من منظور إنساني.
لكنك ترفض رؤية وجهة نظري.
إذا سمحت لنفسك فقط
لرؤية الاستمرارية بأكملها،
أنماط الحياة، ثم سوف تفهمها.
بدلاً من ذلك، فإنك تغلق الفهم عمدًا
كأنك خائف.
ألمها...
أنا لست خائفا.
وما فعله بليك لها.
لقد انتهيت للتو من النظر إلى الوراء
على ذكرياتي الغبية.
لقد حملت ذلك معي لسنوات.
أنا أعرف ما أنت عليه، إدوارد بليك.
لقد عرفت ذلك منذ 25 عامًا.
أي نوع من الرجال يجبر المرأة على ممارسة الجنس؟
ضد إرادتها؟
ما حدث كان منذ 40 عامًا.
- إنه التاريخ. - مرة واحدة فقط.
أنا لست خائفا.
حتى الأجزاء القذرة منه...
انا لا...
...تظل أكثر إشراقا طوال الوقت.
يا إلهي، أنت بحاجة إلى علاج.
ابني!
كان والدي دائما
يصرخ في وجهي...
لوريل جين!
...لأنه يعلم أنها ليست له.
لوريل جين، أليس كذلك؟ ابنة سالي؟
هل لا يستطيع الرجل أن يتحدث إلى ابنة صديقه القديم؟
إنه...
لم تكبر بشكل سيء جدًا بنفسك.
إنه ليس لي..
لا أزال أرى والدتك فيك.
لقد حصلت على عينيها.
هل تتحدث والدتك عني كثيرًا؟
لا.
ولم أستطع الاستمرار
الغضب بعد الآن.
وكان لطيفا فعلا.
اعتقدت أننا قد حسمنا كل هذا منذ وقت طويل.
التقدم في السن،
تحصل على وجهة نظر مختلفة.
هل يستطيع الرجل أن يتحدث إلى...
...ابنة صديقه القديم؟
لا.
لا!
لا، لا، لا.
بليك، أيها الوغد!
لن أدعوك أبدًا بأبي!
أنت على حق.
حياتي عبارة عن مزحة.
حياتي...كل الحياة...
لا معنى له.
أنا أعترض.
ماذا؟
لا أعتقد أن حياتك ليس لها معنى.
ولكن... لماذا؟
لقد...غيرت رأيي.
طوال وجودي،
لقد كنت أتوق لرؤية معجزة ترموديناميكية،
حدث مع احتمالات
عظيم جدًا ضد حدوث ذلك على الإطلاق،
أنه من المستحيل فعليا
مثل الأكسجين الذي يتحول تلقائيا إلى ذهب.
في كل اقتران بشري،
a thousand-million sperms
vie for a single egg.
Multiply those odds
by countless generations,
against the odds
of your ancestors being alive,
meeting,
siring this precise son,
that exact daughter,
until one day,
your mother loves a man
she has every reason to hate.
And out of that union,
of the
thousand-million children
competing for fertilization,
it was you,
only you that emerged.
To distill so specific a form
from that chaos
of improbability,
is like turning air
into gold.
That is
the crowning unlikelihood,
the thermodynamic miracle.
But, if I'm...
if my birth
is a thermodynamic miracle,
you could say that about
anyone else in the world.
Yes. The world
is so full of people,
so crowded
with these miracles,
that they become commonplace.
And we forget...
I forget what they truly are.
Now, from your vantage point,
I see the Earth.
Dry your eyes, Laurie,
for you are life,
rarer than a quark
and unpredictable beyond
the dreams of Heisenberg,
the clay in which the forces
that shape all things
leave their fingerprints
most clearly.
Dry your eyes,
and let's go home.
Not like him.
Building deserted.
- Works here late every night.
- Found his daily planner.
Yesterday's entry...
"Leave for Karnak."
That's his private base
in the Antarctic.
So much
for asking him for help.
This chart,
analysis of global crises.
War, famine,
environmental decline.
Crisis lines converge
mid '90s.
Optimistic.
Crisis arrives decade early,
unless we get lead
on Pyramid Deliveries.
Oh, shit.
Veidt Enterprises holdings
includes Pyramid Deliveries,
Dimensional Developments,
Nova Express,
the Institute
for Extraspatial Studies.
Adrian owns them, Rorschach.
He owns and controls
all of them.
But Veidt was target
of assassin.
Maybe, maybe not.
We need to find Adrian fast.
Rorschach's journal,
November 1st, 1985.
Final entry.
Dreiberg convinced Veidt
is behind everything.
Cannot imagine
more dangerous opponent.
Faster than either of us.
Could kill us both there
in Antarctic snow.
Nobody would ever know.
Return from mission
seems unlikely.
Hope the world
survives long enough
for anyone to read this,
so people will know the truth
of this conspiracy
that Adrian Veidt
is responsible.
For my own part,
I regret nothing.
I've lived life
free from compromise.
I step into the shadow now,
without complaint.
Not the sort of snow
you're used to in California,
Mr. Roth.
I am as pleasantly
surprised by a coke-joke
from the world-famous
Adrian Veidt,
as I am your gracious
invitation to Karnak here.
Your Antarctic retreat
is breathtaking,
to say the least.
And the name, Karnak.
Egyptian in origin, correct?
Yes. You've done
your homework.
Not enough
to keep up with you, I'm sure.
Hello, Mr. Veidt.
You'll be happy to know
the delivery arrived
in perfect condition.
Excellent news, my friends.
I've brought you
an excellent wine to celebrate.
Ah. Ramses II,
also known as Ozymandias,
your namesake as a superhero.
Tell us more about your path
to becoming Ozymandias.
Oh, certainly.
I'd say my journey began
after my parents died.
لقد تركوا لي الكثير من المال،
لكنني أعطيت كل ذلك للجمعيات الخيرية عندما كان عمري 17 عامًا.
أردت أن أثبت أنني قادر على تحقيق أي شيء أريده...
- هل نعد لك العشاء؟ - لا.
العمل يأتي أولاً.
... كان الإرشاد فقط هو الإلهام
من الإنسان الوحيد الذي شعرت معه بأي قرابة،
الإسكندر المقدوني.
كقائد جيش شاب لامع،
اجتاح الإسكندر العديد من البلدان،
حكمت بدون همجية،
وأنشأ أعظم مركز للتعلم في العالم
في مصر.
عازمًا على قياس نجاحي بمقارنته بنجاحه،
عدت إلى خطوات بطلي...
مقابلة نوفا اكسبريس
جاهز لمراجعتك قبل البث.
الكوكب يعج بالأحداث حاليًا،
وأنا بحاجة لمراجعتهم جميعا.
أحتاج إلى المعلومات في شكلها الأكثر تركيزًا.
...حيث يقول البعض أنك تعلمت حتى
كيفية التقاط الرصاصة بيديك العاريتين!
سوف نتقاعد للاستمتاع بهديتك السخية.
نحن نعلم أنك تفضل البقاء بمفردك هنا.
نعم.
لقد وحّد الإسكندر العالم المتحضر...
وحيدا تماما.
ولكن فقط أثناء حياته.
أنا والعالم فقط.
حكمة الفراعنة
ألهمت العالم
للأجيال القادمة بعد رحيلهم.
اعتماد الاسم اليوناني لرمسيس الثاني،
وأسلوب ألكسندر في الركلات الحرة،
بدأت رحلتي... نحو الغزو.
لا غزو الرجال،
لكن الشرور التي تحيط بهم.
تتغير القنوات كل 100 ثانية
إنشاء صور عشوائية،
السماح بإشارات خفية للمستقبل
لتأتي من خلال.
نموذج لغز الغد.
أرى تقابلا
من العنف الذي يهدف إلى تحقيق الرغبات والصور الطفولية،
مثيرة للرغبة في التراجع والتحرر من المسؤولية.
أرى زيادة في الصور الجنسية، مما يشير إلى وجود تيار جنسي
ليس من غير المألوف في أوقات الصراع.
كل هذا يقول الحرب.
سأستثمر وفقا لذلك.
الجميع خائفون، يمكنك أن تشعر بذلك.
لقد قدرت
لم أكن بعيدًا عن ديفيدستاون...
فقط في انتظار بدء سقوط الأسلحة النووية.
كنت متأكدا من ذلك الآن
لقد تم اجتياح المكان
من قبل قطاع الطرق في السفينة.
في نهاية رحلتي،
كل ما تبقى لي الآن هو الانتقام
ضد أولئك الذين قتلوا عائلتي وطاقمي،
وتركني للموت.
ديفيدستاون نام،
مهجورة إلا من الصمت.
من الصعب أن نصدق أننا سنعود إلى المنزل أخيرًا.
سأشرب على ذلك.
وصلت إلى مسكني السابق،
احرص على عدم إثارة الجزارين الذين يحتلونها.
ولم يعلموا أن الموت كان بينهم...
سوف يعرفون عناقه المظلم دون أن يفهموا السبب على الإطلاق.
لكن أحدهم كان مستيقظا.
محمومًا، خشية أن يثير الإنذارات،
لقد انقضضت عليه.
في ظلام الساد،
لقد ضربته بهراوة.
صراخه حاد ومزعج.
لم يأتِ القراصنة، بل جاء شيء أسوأ.
نظرت إلى الوجوه المألوفة،
باستثناء إرهابهم.
بكى الأطفال.
نظرت إلى الشكل الذي تحتي.
من خلال شفتيها المنتفختين والمدميتين، نطقت باسمي.
لقد جاء تفاهم كبير جدًا،
لم يترك أي مجال للعقلانية.
لقد ركضت، لكن معرفتي باللعنة التي حلت بي جعلتني أركض،
الشماتة، والاحتفال بانتصارها الرهيب.
خلف ظهري، كان حشد من لينش يصرخ.
في النهاية، وصلت إلى شاطئ بلون الرماد،
محيط أسود كئيب يمتد أمامي.
كيف وصلت إلى هذا الموقف المروع،
مع الحب، الحب فقط، كدليل لي؟
How had my noble intentions,
led me to atrocity?
Pausing,
I stood, panting, sobbing,
...listening to
the windborne sound
of my pursuers draw closer.
Planning to resume my flight,
I raised my head and saw her.
The black freighter and its
accursed inhabitants
seemed to be waiting,
waiting for me.
They'd come to Davidstown
to collect the only prize
they'd ever valued.
Claim the only soul
they'd ever truly wanted.
I was a horror,
amongst horrors I must dwell.
I swam towards the
anchored freighter.
A rope snaked down.
Spluttering, I grabbed it.
And from the decks above,
a cheer went up,
both gross and black.
It's stench
affronting heaven.
Manners.
Now.
What can I do for you?
We know
you're behind everything.
The Comedian's murder,
Jon's exile.
Christ! Adrian,
we're on the brink
of World War III
because of you.
Well, Nixon
and his attack dog, Blake,
most certainly did more
in that regard.
Have you ever read
the last speech
Kennedy was supposed
to deliver?
"We in this country,
in this generation,
are by destiny,
rather than by choice,
the watchmen
on the walls of freedom."
But in a world of tyranny,
crosshairs watched him.
Blake's, most probably.
What the hell
are you getting at, Adrian?
It was then
that I began to realize
my adventuring
was a...
hollow crusade
against such forces,
a dark comedy clarified
by the Comedian himself
in '66.
I'm sure you remember
the Crimebusters fiasco,
where he discussed
nuclear war's inevitability.
He opened my eyes
to the truth.
Only the best comedians
accomplish that.
That's when I understood
what I must do.
Alexander's methods,
unification by conquest
would not halt the race
toward mutually-assured
destruction
between East and West.
But Alexander was also known
for untying the unsolvable
Gordian knot...
by severing it with a sword.
The same
unconventional solution
would be required
to untangle
our global problems.
And my sword
would be history's
greatest practical joke.
A joke discovered
by Comedian.
Blake was returning
from Nicaragua by airship
when he spotted
my private island.
He investigated and discovered
my artists and scientists
creating a genetically-altered,
monstrous new life-form
and our research
in teleportation.
Teleportation?
But only Jon can teleport.
Jon proved it possible,
and certainly more desirable
than the electric vehicles
he developed.
So, I capitalized
on his endeavors
by developing the basic patent
for the public spark-hydrants
that power his vehicles.
I financed
Dimensional Developments,
and the Institute
for Extraspatial Studies
with the proceeds.
Both developed new technologies
spun-off from Jon's
government research.
But without his guiding mind,
teleportation proved...
limited.
Anything living
died explosively on arrival.
Talking in circles.
You murdered Comedian
to keep him quiet.
Unfortunately for Blake,
I was monitoring
Moloch's residence
when his practiced
cynicism cracked,
and he began to spill fragments
of my plan.
I regret
his accidental involvement.
With the fate of the world,
and all humanity at stake,
I couldn't risk the possibility
of Blake revealing my plan
in its entirety to anyone...
...especially to Jon.
Being too powerful
and unpredictable
to fit my plans,
I plotted his removal
for years.
Thus his past associates
were exposed to radiation
and cultivated as weapons
against Jon's increasingly
fragile attachment to mankind.
With Jon and Blake
neutralized,
your mask-killer investigation
then needed stopping.
I staged
my own assassination attempt
to place me beyond suspicion
and cast doubt on the theory.
The unwitting assassin I hired
was fed a cyanide capsule.
And Rorschach was framed
for Moloch's murder
to close the loose ends.
Adrian, you're talking about
faulty teleportation
and genetic monsters
and ending war.
How does any of this
mad science make sense?
My plan is quite simple.
Teleport my creature
to New York.
The ensuing explosion
will wipe out half the city.
The aftermath will convince
the governments of Earth
that we are under attack
by beings from another world.
Instead of fighting
each other,
for the first time
the human race will unite
against a common foe
and usher in a new age
of global peace.
Adrian, listen to me.
You're not well.
You need help.
I'm just glad we got here
before you had a chance
to try and do it.
Do it?
Dan, I'm not
some comic book villain.
Do you seriously think
I'd explain my masterstroke
if there was even
the slightest chance of you
affecting its outcome?
I did it 35 minutes ago.
Oh, man.
Hm.
Well, it's 11:25.
About time to close up, kid.
Hey, how many times
you gonna read that junk?
This story
don't make sense, man.
That's why I got
to read it over.
And my name's Bernie,
not "kid."
Bernie?
Short for Bernard?
No kidding.
That's my name... too.
Whoa...
What the...
Ah, Jesus, Derf...
Holy...
Oh, my God!
What... what the hell is that?
I had expected us to return
to Earth much earlier.
The interference I had noticed,
it was not a warhead detonation
after all.
So what...
Tachyons.
A squall of tachyons.
But where can they be
coming from?
I had almost forgotten
the delights of uncertainty.
Jon...
I am picking up a strong pulse
from the south-polar region.
Jon, get me out of here, please.
Of course.
No one will doubt
the Earth has met a force
so dreadful
that it must be repelled,
all former enmities aside.
No one must ever
know the truth.
Those who were involved
are dead.
Killers killed by killers
who killed each other.
A lethal pyramid.
And what about us?
Veidt, of course.
Who else has the intelligence
for tachyon interference?
He must have anticipated
my possible discovery
of his plot for some time.
All that stuff in New York,
Adrian planned it?
Yes. He killed Blake
and half of New York.
Excuse me, Rorschach.
I am informing Laurie
ten seconds ago.
These tachyons are muddling
things up.
Jon, wait!
-  Jon!
-  No!
Have to stop him.
Killed Blake
and half of New York.
Yes. He killed Blake
Excuse me, Rorschach.
I am informing Laurie
ten seconds ago.
These tachyons
are muddling things up.
The static is stronger here.
Hiding behind these tachyons
was clever, Veidt.
ولكن هذه اللعبة غبية.
جيد جدا.
إذا كان لا بد لي من متابعة هذا الأمر حتى النهاية المريرة...
و.
بوباستيس، سامحني.
فيدت، لا تفعل ذلك!
هاه، لم أكن متأكدًا حقًا من أن هذا سينجح.
فيدت...
أنت أحمق.
يا للقرف.
لوري!
شيء آخر لم أكن متأكدًا من أنني سأفعله-
أنا أشعر بخيبة أمل، فيدت.
مخيبة للآمال للغاية.
إعادة هيكلة نفسي كانت أول خدعة تعلمتها.
هل كنت تعتقد حقا أن ذلك سيقتلني؟
لقد مشيت عبر الشمس.
لقد رأيت أحداثًا صغيرة جدًا وسريعة جدًا
لدرجة أنه لا يمكن القول بأنها حدثت على الإطلاق.
ولكن انت؟
أنت مجرد رجل.
وهذا الرجل الأكثر ذكاءً في العالم
لا يعني لي شيئًا أكثر من النمل الأبيض الأكثر ذكاءً.
ما هذا يا فيدت؟
سلاح نهائي آخر؟
يمكنك أن تقول ذلك.
هذا فقط في...
لدينا صور مرعبة...
أوه المسيح...
ما أنت على وشك رؤيته قد يصدمك.
...إنه مشهد فظيع للغاية هنا.
...معهد يبحث في أبعاد أخرى.
...لقد مات الملايين هنا هذا المساء.
لا! لا!
هل يمكن أن يكون هذا اتصالاً فضائياً؟
هل تم غزو الأرض؟
القلق العالمي يتزايد..
...وقادة العالم يصدرون
بيانات الدعم في جميع أنحاء العالم.
نحن نسمع الآن أن الزعيم الروسي
وقال جورباتشوف:
إنهم يقيمون التهديد الجديد في نيويورك...
...تزايد الدعوات لعقد قمة سلام فورية
في جنيف بحضور زعماء العالم...
في جهد عالمي متضافر...
حتى روسيا علقت عملها العسكري.
سيداتي وسادتي، هذه أخبار جيدة.
لقد إنتهت الحرب .
لقد إنتهت الحرب.
لقد فعلتها لقد فعلتها!
لقد أنقذت الأرض من الجحيم!
وبعد ذلك سأرفعها نحو اليوتوبيا.
انتظر. التالي؟
هل تعتقد حقا أنك تستطيع النجاة من هذا؟
إذا كشفتني،
سوف تلغى السلام الذي مات من أجله الملايين.
إذا قتلتني
أنت تخاطر بالتحقيقات التي ستكشف عما حدث.
إنه على حق.
فضح هذه المؤامرة
يؤدي إلى مزيد من الدمار على الأرض.
لقد أظهرت قيمة الحياة على المريخ.
إذا أردنا أن نحافظ على الحياة هنا، يجب علينا أن نلتزم الصمت.
أنت على حق، يسوع.
رورشاخ...
نحن...نحن...
علينا أن نتوصل إلى حل وسط بشأن هذا.
لا.
ليس حتى في مواجهة هرمجدون.
لا تتنازل أبدًا.
حسنًا، على الأرجح أنه ليس له أي أهمية.
لا يمكن اعتبار رورشاخ شاهدًا موثوقًا به على الإطلاق.
ما زال...
أعتقد أنني سوف أتأمل في مرصدي الفلكي الآن.
جون؟
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
العودة إلى أمريكا.
يجب إخبار الناس، ويجب معاقبة الشر.
أنت تعلم أنني لا أستطيع أن أدعك تفعل ذلك.
بالطبع. لحماية يوتوبيا فيدت الجديدة.
جسد آخر بين الأسس
لا يحدث فرقًا كبيرًا.
حسنًا...
ماذا تنتظر؟
افعلها.
رورشاخ...
افعلها!
لا!
- لا لا. - دان.
إله.
انا هنا، دان.
لا.
أنا آسف جدا.
مرحباً، جون.
كنت أتمنى أن تتاح لنا فرصة للتحدث.
أعلم أنني سافرت عبر الظهر
من قتل الأبرياء لإنقاذ البشرية.
ولكن كان على شخص ما أن يتحمل هذا الوزن
من تلك الجريمة البشعة الضرورية.
على عكس رورشاخ، أنا أفهم،
دون تبرير أو إدانة.
لم يعد من الممكن أن تكون الشؤون الإنسانية من اهتماماتي.
سأترك هذه المجرة من أجل شيء واحد... أقل تعقيدًا.
لكنك استعدت اهتمامك بالحياة البشرية.
نعم لدي.
أعتقد أنني أرغب في إنشاء بعض منها.
وداعا ادريان.
قبل أن تغادر،
لقد فعلت الشيء الصحيح، أليس كذلك؟
لقد نجح كل شيء في النهاية.
في النهاية؟
لا شيء ينتهي، أدريان.
لا شيء ينتهي أبدًا.
حسنًا، على الرغم من أنه كاد أن يقتلني
مع نوبة قلبية،
هذه هدية عيد الميلاد رائعة.
أنا سعيدة جدًا بعودة طفلتي الصغيرة لوريل.
- لون الشعر، جانبا. - أمي، هل تتذكرين؟
إنه ساندرا وسام هوليس الآن.
أوه!
وسيكون هوليس فخوراً جداً لأنك أخذت اسمه.
لقد كان أقل ما يمكنني فعله لتكريمه.
لقد كان بمثابة الأب الثاني بالنسبة لي.
ولهذا السبب أردت أن أزورها.
أمي، لقد اكتشفت من هو والدي الحقيقي.
أوه يسوع.
أوه، لوريل. أنا آسف جدًا.
أم...
- ما الذي يجب أن تفكر فيه... - أمي، لا يهم.
حياة الناس تأخذهم إلى أماكن غريبة.
إنهم يفعلون أشياء غريبة،
وأحيانا لا يستطيعون التحدث عنها.
أنا أعلم كيف هو الأمر.
أحبك أمي.
لم تفعل أي شيء خاطئ معي أبدًا.
وداعا سام وداعا ساندرا
ولا تنتظري طويلاً لإنجاب الأطفال.
أنا امرأة عجوز.
- وداعا يا أمي. - وداعا يا آنسة جوبيتر.
كما تعلم، ربما لم يكن ذلك
هذه فكرة سيئة جدًا من والدتك
انسى ذلك.
ليس بعد.
لقد كنت تتحدث عن المغامرة مرة أخرى،
وأنا لن أبقى في المنزل لتغيير الحفاضات.
يبدو أن Nite Owl وSilk Spectre رائعين جدًا.
- أعتقد أنني أريد اسمًا جديدًا. - مم؟
و زي أفضل للحماية.
- مم-هم. - شيء جلدي.
بالتأكيد.
وقناع.
أوه...
- ربما مسدس. - مم...
سيمور، أين كنت؟
البعد X؟
لقد حصلت للتو على وجبة غداء من Burgers 'n' Borscht.
لا تقل ذلك!
لن أسمح بالتحدث باللغة الروسية في هذا المكتب،
اتفاقية السلام التقبيلية أم لا.
ماذا تفعل؟
حسنًا، كنت سأتناول غدائي.
مات ثلاثة ملايين من سكان نيويورك،
ولم تكن واحدا منهم.
سيمور، اللعنة عليك!
لقد بقي لديك صفحتين أخريين لتملأهما قبل أن تأكل.
اعتقدت أن عمودك--
حسنا، لقد فكرت خطأ.
لا يجوز لأحد أن يقول أشياء سيئة
لم يعد هناك أي حديث عن "أصدقائنا القدامى الطيبين"، الروس.
وهكذا انتهى الأمر بعمود من صفحتين.
احصل على بعض الحشو في مكان ما.
يقول روبرت ريدفورد
سيترشح للرئاسة في عام 88.
سيمور، لا تحترم السخافات
مع التغطية.
لا أحد يريد ممثل رعاة البقر في البيت الأبيض.
ثم أعتقد أنه شيء ما
من ملف الكرنك؟
نعم نعم.
كل ما هو ضمن قدراتك المحدودة.
فقط تحمل المسؤولية مرة واحدة في حياتك.
افعل ما تريد.
أترك الأمر بالكامل بين يديك.
♪ هل يمكنك احتواء الانهيارات العصبية؟ ♪
وجبة خفيفة بحجم اللقمة تعود إلى العصر الذري
هذا سيجعلك تتوهج من الرأس حتى القدمين.
♪ هل يمكنك احتواء الانهيارات العصبية؟ ♪
سلسلة من ردود الفعل من إرضاء النكهة
وهذا سيجعل براعم التذوق لديك تنفجر.
♪ هل يمكنك احتواء الانهيارات العصبية؟ ♪
تساقط الفواكه ومركز منصهر لذيذ
وهذا سوف يأخذك طوال الطريق إلى الصين.
♪ هل يمكنك احتواء الانهيارات العصبية؟ ♪
مم، ممتلداونز!